In 1995 a man wrote a letter from his
prison cell. In this
letter he said that more than
30 years ago he watched his mother murder
his four-year-old
sister by stomping her to
death. That letter triggered a new
investigation into a case
that should have been properly
investigated in the first place. This is
the case of Michele
Morgan and a story that
should never have been forgotten.
Hello, welcome to my True Criminelle
podcast. As ever, you are very, very
welcome. Today's case is
about a four-year-old girl who was seen
by doctors again and
again and still sent back to
the home that would kill her. It's about
the future a little girl
never got to have. Well,
the person who took that future from her
went on living their life.
Before I tell you about this
incredibly sad story, a quick trigger
warning as ever. This case does involve
the murder of a child
and as I always, always say, your mental
health comes first. So
please look after yourself. So
with that, let's get on with today's
heartbreaking case about
Michele LeAnn Morgan and a story
that should never have been forgotten. So
we are going to begin
this case in the late 1950s
with a man called Bill Morgan who was
serving in the United States
Air Force. Now Bill had two
young children from previous
relationships. There was George who was
born in 1952 and there was
Michele born in 1957. Now George and
Michele were half siblings
because they had different
mothers. Michele's mother actually
passed away and I believe Bill and
George's mother got divorced.
So in the late 1950s, Bill was stationed
overseas in Prestwick Air Base in
Scotland over here in
the UK and while he was there, he met a
local woman called Mary
Rae. The couple fell in love
and married and they actually went on to
have a daughter called
Sharon together whilst they
were in Scotland. Now around this time,
Bill received a new
posting back in America at Scott
Air Force Base in St. Clair County in
Illinois. So in 1960, Mary and Sharon
left their home in Scotland
and emigrated to America to be with Bill.
So by 1961, Bill, Mary and
Sharon were now living together
in a small farmhouse near Mascuta about
four miles away from the
Scott Air Force Base and they also
had Bill's two children, George and
Michele, now with them who up until this
point had been staying
with their grandparents whilst Bill was
posted overseas. George was
around about eight years old
by this time and Michele was around
about three or four years old
around this time. So when Mary
arrived in Illinois, she became
stepmother to both George and Michele
and with Bill working
long shifts at the base. The children
spent most of their time at home under
Mary's care and at the
time this case takes place, Mary was
actually pregnant with twins
as well. So you get the idea,
it was a pretty hectic household. She had
Sharon who was very young
still around about a year old,
she had Bill's two young children from
his previous relationships, Michele and
George and then she was
pregnant as well with twins. Now the
family's home was rural and fairly
isolated with few neighbors
and little outside contact. Life around
Scott Air Force Base was
often transient with families
regularly arriving and departing but away
from the base in the
surrounding rural areas. Homes
were spread out and neighbors tended to
keep themselves to
themselves and so the result was
a quiet isolated-ish setting. I mean
obviously the families were social, it's
a military area but it
was a rural farmhouse and crucially this
meant that there were fewer
chances for anyone outside the
household to notice what was going on
inside of this newly
blended family's home.
So in the year after Mary arrived in
Illinois, Michele began
turning up at the Scott Air Force
Base hospital again and again with
injuries that were difficult to ignore.
She was only three or
four years old during this period yet she
was treated more than 20
times for everything from
bruises and burns to fractures. Some of
the injuries were severe,
things like a broken arm,
a broken nose, multiple injuries to the
back of her head, burns
across her scalp and her back,
deep bruising on her thighs and her
chest. Other injuries were smaller but
constant, perpetual,
like bruises, cuts, abrasions to her face
and abdomen and patches of
hair missing from her head.
Each time Mary explained them away as
accidents or fainting
spells, insisting that Michele
collapsed without warning. But inside the
home the reality was
clearly far far darker. George
Michele's half-brother later described
months of escalating
violence, beatings with objects,
forced to punishments and long stretches
of neglect in which
Michele received little care
or comfort. Now George was a child
himself, he was eight, but
he saw enough to understand
that what was happening to his sister was
not normal and not
accidental as Mary claimed.
And George would later say that he was
himself physically abused by
Mary. He described being hit
by the buckle end of a military air force
belt. He was stabbed in the
chest with a fork. One time
he was kicked in the teeth because he
dared to move when she
told him not to move a muscle.
He also claimed that when he was seven he
was playing with several
girls who were neighbours
and his stepmother called him over and
asked him whether he had
been playing with dolls.
Mary was devoted to her religion and
asked George whether he
believed in the Bible and God
and instructed him to tell the truth as
the good book commanded. Now
even though George had been
playing with dolls, with his neighbours,
he didn't want to admit to it so Mary
took him to a closet
that contained the vacuum cleaner. She
wrapped the cord around his
neck and tightened it until
George blacked out. Wow! What is it with
these people who use religion as an
excuse for violence?
Maybe if she had herself read the good
book I doubt she would
have found anywhere that says
punish your child by strangling them with
the electric cord of the vacuum cleaner.
So poor little Michele, she has been
seen by doctors over 20
times already. It's 1961.
Mary only arrived in the US in 1960 so
this is a really
really short period of time.
Now doctors grew concerned enough to
admit Michele for nearly
a month into the hospital
to investigate possible epilepsy. I'm not
sure how they came to that
conclusion but I guess you know
Mary is telling them that Michele is
fainting a lot and falling
over so it makes sense that
that's something that they would
investigate as well as the abuse you
would think. But anyway
during Michele's month in hospital she
didn't once have a
single seizure. Not once.
But what the staff did notice was that
every time Mary walked into that hospital
Michele became visibly distressed crying
and screaming. But
despite the pretty damn obvious
signs nobody intervened. The signs were
there. I mean playing
devil's advocate in 1960 and 1961
there was no meaningful child protection
framework. Mandatory
reporting did not yet exist
and follow-up was inconsistent at best.
But still it's darn right frustrating
because at this point
this little girl's life could have been
saved. But instead the
hospital treated the injuries,
documented them and sent Michele home
each time with no system
in place to protect her.
So on Wednesday the 9th of August 1961
eight-year-old George and four-year-old
Michele were playing
outside. At some point that afternoon
Michele made a small
mistake. Something so minor that
George later couldn't even remember what
that mistake was. But
whatever it was it was enough
it was enough to set Mary off. Mary
accused Michele of lying.
She obviously does not like
lying in the same way that she accused
George of lying. She's
obviously somewhat obsessed with
children lying to her. So she accuses
Michele of lying. She grabbed her
dragged her to an outdoor
rinse tub filled with rainwater and
forced Michele into it. George watched
as Mary held Michele
underwater lifting her only long enough
for the little girl to gasp
and cry before pushing her
head under again. When Mary finally
pulled Michele from the tub she dragged
her inside the house to
the kitchen. George followed to the
doorway and saw Mary force Michele to
lie on her back on the
kitchen floor. Mary was wearing square
heeled shoes kind of solid
blocky 1960s style shoes with
really hard edges. And what happened next
stayed with George for the
rest of his life. Mary lifted
her foot and brought it down on
Michele's chest. Michele is four years
old. Mary did it more than
once. She did it I believe around about
four or five times. Each blow driven by
the weight and shape
of those square heels. George later said
that every time Mary's foot struck
Michele's small body
bounced like a rag doll. Now poor little
Michele she was seriously injured
but she didn't die straight away. I mean
she's been half drowned
viciously stomped on so you can imagine
the pain that she would have
been in. And later that evening
as the family sat down for dinner it was
obvious that Michele was
seriously ill with internal
injuries. She was quiet and pale and part
way through the meal she
began vomiting blood clots
onto her plate. Clots that George would
later describe as looking
like raw liver. Now Bill was
home by this point and he looked startled
because of course he hadn't
been there during the day. He
had no idea apparently he had no idea of
what had taken place during
the day. He asked Mary what was
wrong with his daughter. Now I don't
understand this bit because George said
the two adults stepped
out of the room to talk. As Mary left she
told Michele to finish
her dinner. What an absolute
callous bitch. This poor little
four-year-old girl is throwing up blood
clots and Mary is saying
finish your dinner. I'm not entirely sure
why Bill didn't get his
daughter help straight away.
She's throwing up blood clots. What the
actual hell? And to make
this fact worse, years later
a forensic pathologist said that had
Michele got help straight away the
injuries would have been
survivable. It wasn't until the next
morning when Michele complained of
feeling dizzy and nauseous
and had weakness in the legs that she was
rushed to the hospital at Scott Air Force
Base. But tragically
despite the doctor's efforts Michele's
injuries were just too
severe and two days after the
assault on August the 11th 1961 Michele
died for a massive internal trauma.
Michele's funeral was
held the following day. During the
service George tried to tell relatives
that his stepmother had
murdered her but nobody listened to him.
Mary had told the
authorities that Michele had fallen
from a wood pile whilst chasing rabbits
because Michele was apparently always
falling and feinting
despite spending a month in hospital and
not a single fall or a
single faint. That's what she
told the authorities. A local newspaper
at the time even reported
that Michele had died after
falling whilst chasing a rabbit under a
bush and that was the version of the
story that people who
knew the family accepted and within a
year of Michele's death the
family was gone. Bill, Mary,
George, Sharon and the twins because Mary
is now given birth to twins.
She was pregnant whilst she
killed her stepdaughter but they all
left. Michele remained
behind in an unmarked grave
because her family couldn't even be
bothered to get her a gravestone
and with that Michele's
real story was buried with her.
Michele's autopsy was performed by Air
Force Captain Dr Brian
Harrold the pathologist on duty
at Scott Air Force Base. His examination
revealed catastrophic
injuries. Michele had a torn section
of bowel, massive internal bleeding and
had lost more than half of
her blood. Losing that much
blood internally means that she would
have been in extreme pain for
hours. She also had patterned
bruising repeated distinctively shaped
marks that told Dr Harrold
that she'd been struck with an
object and basically not injured in a
fall. He didn't know
exactly what the patterns and the
bruising was because he had no idea about
the shoes but obviously in hindsight we
now know it was those
shoes but that's the force that Mary used
on that little girl.
Michele's official cause of death
was recorded as internal bleeding caused
by blunt force trauma
to the chest and abdomen.
Dr Harrold also found signs of previous
harm, two healed rib
fractures, a healing skull injury and
older wounds on her head and her thigh.
These injuries showed a
longer history of abuse
separate from the final assault that
killed her but nothing
happens. In fact the family leaves.
Three years later in 1964 the Air Force
conducted a follow-up
review of Michele's case.
Several Air Force physicians re-examined
the autopsy and
concluded that her injuries were
the result of abuse going so far as
identifying her injuries as
consistent with battered child
syndrome. Now this was a newly recognized
concept at the time. I think
at the time of the original
autopsy this wasn't a thing but three
years later it was. But
either way the original autopsy
showed that there was something dodgy. A
follow-up review showed
that there was something dodgy.
So now Mary's arrested right? Of course
she wasn't. Even with
those findings no agency
took responsibility for investigating. So
basically the Air Force said
the assault occurred off base
and it was therefore a civilian matter.
The local authorities on
the other hand argued that the
family were military dependents and
should fall under military
jurisdiction. So each side were
arguing and waiting for the other side to
act. And neither side
actually did act. Um hello? A child
was murdered? Who gives a crap? Who
investigates? Just somebody do it.
Somebody investigate. It's
crazy right. And then 15 years later it
transpired that Michele's
case had sat untouched in the
coroner's office. When a retiring county
coroner was clearing out old files
Michele's incomplete
paperwork surfaced. He didn't remember
the case so he listed
pneumonia as the cause of death
and filed the death certificate in 1976.
15 years after Michele
died. Did no one think to
double check anything? Like I don't know.
Check hospital charts,
review her long history of
injuries. I mean it wasn't malicious but
it sure as hell was negligence. And
either way her death
certificate was filed 15 years after
Michele died and said she died from
pneumonia. What the hell?
So altogether there was a series of
mistakes that kind of helped keep
Michele's case buried
and the truth of her murder hidden for
what's going to be 35 years.
[Music]
So let's fast forward to over 30 years
later in 1995. George
Morgan was now in his 40s and was
serving a 45-year prison sentence in
Jefferson City, Missouri.
George Morgan was now a convicted
child abuser serving three consecutive
15-year sentences for one
rape and two acts of sodomy
against his 10-year-old stepdaughter. So
just as Mary abused her stepchildren
George grew up to do
the same thing. It beggars belief doesn't
it? When you grow up feeling
abandoned and then abused by
a step-parent you know how that feels. So
why would you then go on
to do that to another child?
I know the abuse was different in the
sense that Mary's abuse was
physical and you know George's
was sexual but come on surely as a human
being you would make sure
that children in your care
do not suffer the way that you did. But
that's the thing with
trauma it doesn't always produce
the opposite behavior. Sometimes it
produces the same behavior not because
the person necessarily
wants to cause harm but because their
sense of boundaries was
destroyed their understanding of
normal was damaged abuse from a young age
affects the brain's wiring
so empathy can be disrupted
things like that. Now George carried
trauma over Michele's death
for decades and that would have
shaped the person that he became and it
just goes to show how bad the abuse in
Michele's home must
have been. But it's never an excuse it's
never a justification
obviously it's just a psychological
reality. Not always obviously a lot of
people don't go on to do the same thing
but far too often it is.
And that's why it's so important that
people get that help
before they go on to offend.
Anyway apparently George denied the
charges but that's the sentence he got.
But anyway during George's incarceration
he began researching his
family history. I don't know why
I'm going to speculate it was something
to do with his birth
mother perhaps who her and Bill
had divorced when he was young so you
know I'm guessing that's
what it was to do with but it's
pure speculation. But as part of that
search he requested a copy of
Michele's death certificate
and what he received made absolutely no
sense because the
certificate had been issued as we know
15 years after Michele's death in
January 1976 and the cause of death was
listed as viral pneumonia.
Something George knew was not possible
because he was there he saw
what happened to Michele.
So on August the 21st 1995 he wrote to
the St Clair County
coroner's office explaining
that the certificate was wrong and that
when he was eight years
old he had watched his sister
being murdered by his stepmother. His
letter eventually reached
coroner Rick Stone and Stone
later admitted that he was skeptical I
mean George is in prison he was a
convicted child abuser so
you're going to be damn skeptical. But
there was something in
George's tone the bluntness the lack
of self-interest because he said he
didn't want to deal which was a big one
you know when you say
you don't want to deal that's a big one
and that made Stone pay
attention and he wrote back and
they exchanged letters and eventually
Stone contacted the Illinois
State Police and on January
the 31st 1996 Stone and cold case
detective Kurt Sachtleben travelled to
Missouri to speak with
George in the prison. When Stone asked
why George was coming forward George
confirmed that he didn't
want anything in return he just wanted
justice for Michele and
Stone believed him and in 1996
finally the case was reopened.
So investigators are faced with kind of
an immediate problem how
do you prove a homicide
from 1961 but they had one advantage
Michele had died at a military hospital
and military hospitals
do not destroy their records so their
search led them to Air Force
captain Dr. Brian Harrold who
was the pathologist who had performed
Michele's original autopsy more than
three decades earlier.
He was now living in Florida and had his
own private practice when
they called him Dr. Harrold
actually told them that he had been
waiting over 30 years for
somebody to ask about Michele.
He had been unhappy with the
circumstances of her death I'm not
surprised. Now there has been
criticism over the years about how so
many people failed Michele and generally
Michele was clearly
failed by a lot of people but in the case
of Dr. Harrold I think the failure was
largely bureaucratic
you know he did his job he completed the
autopsy he documented the injuries he
filled in the report
and then what happened after that was
outside of his control and as
we've seen you know there was
this jurisdictional confusion going on
between the military
hospital and the county coroner's
office with each side saying it was the
other side's
responsibility so there wasn't much he
could do and the case just kind of
slipped through the cracks could people
have done more people can
always do more but the system in place at
the time made it far too
easy for a child like Michele
to be lost in paperwork but anyway the
pathologist remembered the case well and
confirmed everything
that George described seeing George had
even described the shoes
Mary was wearing and these
matched the findings from Dr. Harrold's
suspicions 30 years earlier so ultimately
Dr. Harrold confirmed
that Michele's injuries were consistent
with a child being
stomped on and definitely not
pneumonia as part of the reopened
investigation the rediscovered autopsy
and surviving medical
charts were reviewed by medical staff at
Scott Air Force Base their
findings matched Harrold's
exactly basically everybody that looked
into this just said you know
she did not die from pneumonia
she was beaten to death so with these
sort of independent medical
opinions now aligning across
the decades the truth was coming to light
but the investigators
still needed to confirm it
so in December 1996 they made the
decision to exhume Michele's body after
35 years they needed
to know whether her remains would still
reflect the injuries described in the
autopsy and George's
account now it was pretty grim the small
wooden coffin had not held
up well in the 35 years in
the ground after opening Michele's grave
investigators had to
sift through this soil
for the bones and bone fragments but it
was the only way to
confirm what had happened to her
forensic pathologist Dr. Janice Opphoven
examined the remains and
ordered x-rays of Michele's bones
and even after decades in the ground
Michele's bones still
carried the marks of the violence
that she had endured two of her ribs
showed healing fractures
her left upper arm had a
significant healing break her nose had
been broken the back of her
skull bore signs of repeated
impact injuries Opphoven said that the
facial trauma was so severe
that had Michele survived
she would likely have needed
reconstructive surgery that's
horrendous none of Opphoven's
findings contradicted the original
autopsy in 1961 Dr.
Harrold had been able to see the
soft tissue injuries you know the torn
stomach the internal bleeding the
bruising in the shape
of the of the shoes but those soft tissue
injuries they disappear
obviously with decomposition
and then what remained of the bones and
35 years later the bones
told exactly the same story
a story that matched what George had
described so even after 35 years
Michele's body still spoke
for her and what it said was enough to
move the case forward and find that
despicable woman that
did this to her so cold case detectives
tracked down Michele's
stepmother Mary Morgan in west
Columbia Texas she was still married to
Michele's father Bill and together they
had built an entirely
new life they had four children now of
their own so besides George
and Michele who weren't Mary's
biological children they had between them
two boys and two girls we know about
Sharon then there was
the twins and then there was another girl
and Mary and Bill they
were now working get this as
missionaries for a local church in the
community the couple were known for their
devotion to children
including their work with orphans in
Mexico now I do not
want to talk disparagingly
about the amazing work that genuinely
amazing people do but it
ain't half a good cover for
people like this that aren't genuine I
don't know whether it's people
wanting to give the appearance
that they're good community orientated
people or whether they do it
to redeem themselves somehow
feel better about their sins of the past
now the skeptical side of
me says it's probably not the
latter but the former it makes a good
cover story in fact after Mary had been
charged pastor Hankins
of the Christian centre church was
allowed to visit her and told her that
they weren't ashamed
or embarrassed of her and there were a
lot of people praying
for her to which Mary said
quote "I know that because I've got peace"
end quote how exactly
could she have peace
unless she didn't care therefore
missionary work was never really genuine
was it I don't believe
so when detectives questioned Mary about
Michele she claimed she didn't remember
she said she didn't recall broken ribs
she didn't recall the
month-long hospitalisation
she insisted she had no memory of
anything unusual on
December the 6th 1996 a reporter
stationed outside the house called the
police to say that the
Morgans were loading their van
and preparing to leave town officers
intercepted them in Montgomery County
Texas so if you don't
remember anything then what the hell are
you fleeing for huh
anyway Mary said that they were
driving to Illinois to speak with an
attorney the authorities didn't believe
her and she was arrested
[Music]
in February 1997 a grand jury in Illinois
indicted Mary Morgan on one count of
murder and two counts
of involuntary manslaughter one for
causing death during an
assault and one for causing death
through corporal punishment i.e punishing
Michele in a way that
caused fatal injuries
although Mary was indicted for murder she
couldn't face the death
penalty and this was because the
crime occurred in 1961 so she had to be
sentenced under the laws of
that time and the death penalty
in 1961 had been ruled unconstitutional
therefore 30 odd
years later life in prison
was the maximum that she could get now
after the indictment Mary's
legal team negotiated a plea
agreement and Mary agreed to plead guilty
to involuntary
manslaughter which under the law
at the time i.e in 1997 carried a maximum
term of eight years still
not enough but that was the
maximum term but of course the judge
won't be able to actually sentence under
the 1997 law but that
was the term that Mary agreed to when she
pleads guilty Mary was
undergoing cancer treatment at the
time and her lawyer said that she
accepted the deal because she wanted to
put the case behind her
and reduce the strain on her health now
her bail was set at a
million dollars and she posted it
and remained under house arrest whilst
awaiting sentencing so
because Mary had pled guilty under
the plea agreement there was no trial and
the case moved straight to
sentencing at the hearing
Mary's four biological children supported
her they supported their mother insisting
that she was innocent they had grown up
with a very very
different version of their mother
a woman they believed in their heads was
loving devout and
incapable of the violence described
in court but and i said in their heads
because the cold case team's
investigation revealed
that after Michele's death Mary's four
biological children had collectively
visited emergency rooms
more than 150 times before the age of
five injuries included
things like burns after an
iron fell on one of them lacerations
ingesting penicillin falling on the
stomach from a bunk bed
now given these findings it's really
bizarre that the children
defended her 150 times before
the age of five i don't even know what to
say about that i mean if
they were defending her
because she genuinely hadn't done
anything that would make more sense
because it would make sense
that she might have treated her
stepchildren different to
her biological children but 150
times in hospital she clearly didn't
treat them any different and in fact the
forensic pathologist
dr jenice ophoven believed that the
children were abused and
the medical findings basically
confirmed that so why did the children
deny that now this could be a sign of
trauma bonding which
is like a stockholm syndrome-esque type
of thing it's not the same
but it's that kind of idea um
trauma bonding is more common in families
when a caregiver controls
every aspect of a child's
safety fear survival the caregiver kind
of alternates love and
cruelty and the child's
instinct is to cling to them rather than
rejecting them and
that's not because it's
affection or agreement with the abuse
they're getting it's
literally a survival mechanism
i mean i don't know what was going on um
that's a possibility i mean
it would be something like
that for them to be denying what was
clearly abuse but what also
astounds me is Bill Morgan
also defended his wife neshawn and george
were his biological
children as any parent will know
you put your children first period Bill
told the court that george
was lying to reduce his own
sentence he turned on his own son now i
understand i mean you know
it's difficult with george because
he was you know a convicted child abuser
by this point so i'm guessing
there's you know going to be
um some animosity there but he still
defended Mary even if he
didn't like george the adult
george was a child when this abuse was
happening and michael was
dead for god's sake Bill claimed
he didn't remember how Michele died
quote "there was no reason to
go into detail she was gone"
end quote you would think the fact that
your child has died is
enough reason to go into detail
you would think the fact that the
murderer is going to be looking after
your future children
your other children is also a good reason
to go into detail do you
not think i don't get it
he knew what was going on in my opinion i
mean Michele was taken
to the hospital 20 times
doctors had repeatedly suspected abuse
yet Bill repeatedly dismissed their
concerns as accidents
his other children 150 times so he knew
what was going on he said he remembered a little of that
hazy day and he had no reason to doubt
his wife okay you had no
reason to doubt your wife
seriously your children were taken to
hospital 150 times
Michele 20 times she was vomiting
blood clots which you apparently don't
remember on that hazy day
i mean that's disgusting to
say that your child vomiting a blood clot
is hazy you're going to remember that a hundred years
hazy you're going to remember that a
hundred years later let
alone 30 years later and you did
nothing now obviously Bill was never
charged with anything so this is just my
opinion i just don't
see how he did not know what was going on
but it is my opinion and a
lot of other people's opinions
if you read forums on this case now under
modern guidelines the charge of
involuntary manslaughter
that Mary had pleaded guilty to carried a
maximum sentence of eight
years which we have established
however under the law in effect in 1961
the maximum penalty for
involuntary manslaughter was
five years and so that was all the judge
could give her no matter
how severe the abuse or how
long it had gone unpunished all that she
could get was five years it's
disgusting isn't it this was
to prevent ex post facto punishment
meaning that you can't punish someone
more harshly using laws
that didn't exist at the time of the
crime which i do understand
the logic in some cases it makes
sense i mean if the crime was for
stealing a bag of sweets in 1960 and the
punishment was a fine
and then 20 years later the punishment
was getting your hand
chopped off i can see why
you would use the punishment at the time
because the odds are the
person probably wouldn't have
risked having their hands chopped off and
stolen the bag of sweets
but this is murder and i'm not
sure it should apply to murder or
manslaughter it's actually
manslaughter isn't it that she
pled guilty to but i'm not sure it should
apply you know Michele's
life was stolen from her
Mary got to live the rest of her life as
if nothing had happened
five years was an insult
to the memory of Michele so Mary Morgan
was sentenced to five
years in an illinois state
prison she served her time and was
released in 2001 and after that she
vanished from public record
george was released from prison in 2023
he remains under strict
supervision until 2036
and is still legally serving his time but
in the community i mean he
abused a child should he be
walking free i don't think so and i could
say a lot more about what i
think but this is Michele's
story and what george did do was a good
thing by telling the truth
and bringing Michele's story
to light and when the truth did finally
surface it couldn't undo
the past but it ensured that
Michele was seen and heard and
remembered and this was proven when the
community came together
to get Michele a headstone because
remember she had no headstone just a
temporary marker supplied
by the funeral home however after
george's confession reopened
the case the local community
raised the money to finally give her a
proper stone and in the
end it was the community
who ensured that Michele was finally
honored and remembered you know a
headstone may be small but
it stands as proof that her story was
heard and she is not
going to be forgotten again
and that's why i do cases like this
because that little girl she would have
been forgotten if it
wasn't for her brother for the community
she literally would have
been forgotten and so covering
cases like this i think is important
because people need to
remember her because she didn't
just lose her life she lost her future
and the world as i've said
before when other children
are murdered it's the world that loses
something when a child is
taken away because the world
benefits from everybody who knows what
Michele would have gone on to do the
lives that she would
have gone on to touch who knows but she
never got that chance
anyway that is everything as ever
you take care and i will see you back
here for another case at
my True Criminelle podcast bye